Augustine Tonia Davidson

10 N Pennewell Dr., Wilmington, DE 19809 (267) 333-5052 tgusd1@icloud.com
AKA: T-Gus Davidson



Objective

To leverage my extensive experience in desktop computing support, maintenance, customer service, and desktop publishing, along with advanced business strategy and leadership skills acquired through my MBA, to enhance the operational efficiency and strategic growth of your organization. I am committed to ensuring optimal performance by helping in installing, diagnosing, repairing, maintaining, and upgrading desktop hardware, laptops, phones, peripherals, and applications. My strengths include prompt and accurate troubleshooting, end-user support, graphic design, and meticulous documentation.

Education

Tuazama Universal Leadership Academy, School of Management (TULSOM) Philadelphia, PA

MBA Certificate, Business Administration, February 2024

- Advanced Business Strategy: Strategic Management, Thinking, and Decision Making
- Financial Acumen: Financial Management
- Leadership Excellence: Honed Leadership Capabilities, ready to inspire and lead teams
- Global Perspective: Poised for triumph in an interconnected world

St. Patrick's High School

Monrovia, Liberia High School Diploma, 1987

West Africa Computer Science Institute (WACSI)

Monrovia, Liberia Basic Computer Operator's Certificate, July 1988

University of Liberia

Monrovia, Liberia Math Major / Physics Minor (Dropped out due to war), 1988 – 1990

Key Skills

- Data Entry
- Good Prompt Engineering Skills (OpenAI Chat GPT)
- Software Installation & Uninstallation
- Can easily learn and work with varied software packages
- Minor Hardware Repairs
- Secretarial Duties (MS Word, Excel, Publisher, PowerPoint)
- Desktop Publishing & Graphic Design
- Troubleshooting & Technical Support
- Customer Service
- Strategic Management & Decision Making
- Financial Management
- Leadership & Team Development

Professional Experience

Administrative Manager

KPAH Security Services
Paynesville, Liberia
August 2020 – April 2024

- Managed administrative tasks and coordinated office operations.
- Oversaw staff schedules and ensured efficient workflow.
- Maintained client relations and handled inquiries effectively.

IT Officer

Aries Security Services
Paynesville, Liberia
May 2007 – August 2020

- Provided comprehensive IT support, troubleshooting hardware and software issues.
- Installed and maintained security software.
- Trained staff in new technology implementations.

Computer Operator

Shell Top Inc. Monrovia, Liberia April 2006 – December 2006

- Operated and maintained computer systems and peripheral equipment.
- Performed efficient data entry and information processing.

Computer Operator / EDP Officer

PIMEX Trading (Import/Export)
Monrovia, Liberia
October 2003 – August 2004, June 1988 – December 1990

- Managed electronic data processing operations.
- Ensured accurate data entry and system updates.

Desktop Publisher / Trainer / Internet Service Guide

Vision 20/20 Marcory Abidjan, La Cote d'Ivoire 1996 – 2000

- Conducted training sessions on desktop publishing software.
- Designed graphics for certificates, business cards, letterheads, brochures, banners, and more.
- Provided internet service guidance and technical support.

Languages

• English: Proficient (Spoken/Written)

• French: Good (Spoken/Written)

I am eager to bring my technical skills, extensive experience, and dedication, along with my business and leadership training, to your organization.